[Music] Have
mercy on the poor, Chanaka
Dantu, if you
don't throw money [Music]
Give
more work, do the money,
keep the lock closed
[Music]
[Music] So there is
only land, we should
also close the platform, support the hill, this is the solution, if Nathila knows the
evil year, the
sunflower will be destroyed, there will be benefit for the sunflower by closing the land, the crop will be good, whatever
God wishes
[Music] [Music] [
Music] On this
day, God listens to the land, all the crops will be good, the landlord will do the
sunflower and the string will be good,
[Music]
Wow, what a beautiful flower has ripened, look at the bill, the beautiful
sunflower flower has burst
[Music]
Oh, the puja is great, if you worship, the flower will be good, I will
not give you money, the dancer, the flower, all the photos are
fine
[Music]
Keep the cart, keep the cart, who is there, keep the cart
Look, how beautiful the sunflower flower is, come on, my friend [Music] [Music]
Oh,
everything has happened too
[Music]
Hey, pick up the photo, sorry, I am not from my side,
pick up the photo, sorry, h  Reels banwa j Savitri
din jo reels banle 5 lakh views jala log
maane hum jodi ko satya banaao Savitri kahe
kitna praise kalo aaj aao couples reels banba ae
hum reels ban de suno mu scooty chabi aur
recording karo
[Music]
background bh to aa pakho
[Music] arre arre arre arre arre arre
ye aankhon ko dekh
drive
[Screaming sound]
[Laughter] didi
badmaash sab ho
[Music]
wow guys look look what it beautiful
flower garden [Music] yes it's
mind blowing ga beautiful environment ke bhali hey deri hey chalo
photo boreda bhi shahar bhi mil office dekh
[Music]
oh god kaun ho babu babu aap mauti daya kar
phool sab nahin bahu daya karant
phool nahin bahar j daya kar photo uthantu hey
you destroy the aparish Disgusting tik ke
bhi civic sense nahi
o madam ka ko
malik tik
[Music]
ko ela tu party chup kar chup raho nahi to bhul
nahi to man ko bhul pau bhul  Ask for a
pola,
forget the girls, the
rich people, see the drama, everything has started,
come on
[Music]
So everything is fine, God, I
always get the lotus fruit, yes,
keep the car, Muni, the car, you
start it, the engine starts, get it to the
mechanic,
hey friend, get the
mechanic, hey Sandhya,
who will do it,
oh my God Manish ji, the car is in trouble, the car will also get damaged, the
mechanic will not get it, the
hotel's lock will be fixed, the mechanic will fix it, the
hotel's lock will be fixed, tonight, the
hotel's lock will be fixed,
brother, today you have blessings
[Laughter]
Please brother,
adjust and
ask Babu, I am
not ready,
hey Babu, who is the soul,
hey, no, Babu, I have no
objection, you cannot find shelter,
uncle, I am here
today, I am safe, Babu, I will refuse, Babu, then I will agree,
let's
sing, we are ready, we are here, O God, Devi
Khushila post yes
agree today I am at home friend please go then make
arrangements for food yes yes I am going I have made Khechudi with my own hands
Devi
Babu it is fine there is no water here
[Music]
Oh friend this uncle is making the financial situation bad so he
consoles me even on a mistake he is very
kind hearted please forgive me okay
[Music]
You stop and tell Suji to uncle so that I can be a guest it is a good
fortune if I have made a mistake please forgive me
uncle please forgive me on some auspicious occasion
happiness please
spoil my hard work sethi makes me very sad [Music]
Oh who cares for everyone I do
not forgive any mistake even God forgives me
Bhabhi please forgive me
all the things call me uncle yours you say your own words your
own people
refuse happiness please uncle refuse me sleep
Bansi Bhai okay Raghu Dada please keep it in mind if you don't tie the knot you will be
very surprised
[Music]
we